Jared Sasser

- Email kid_icarus3@yahoo.com
- Cell 920-202-0146
- GitHub https://github.com/KidIcarus1337
- LinkedIn https://www.linkedin.com/pub/jared-sasser/40/562/521
- Appleton, WI

Intro

I am a web developer. My focus is on the front-end, but I have some experience in the back-end as well in Node.js and Python. I have taught myself over the last couple of years with the aid of several online courses and occasional help of an experienced mentor.

Tech Skills

- HTML5
- CSS3
- JavaScript
- iQuery
- Twitter Bootstrap
- slick
- Git
- Node.js
- Express.js
- Bash/Linux
- Python
- Firebase DB

Work Experience

Professional Experience - Web Developer, February 2015 - Present

High Altitude Science

Web Developer, February 2015 - March 2015

- Designed and developed the front-end for the Weather Balloon Flight Simulator web app
- Front-end developed with HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Bootstrap, slick, autoNumeric
- Built as a single-page app. This involved using slick to set up a slider that separated the three portions of the simulator one for the input parameters (launch date, burst altitude, etc.), one for the starting coordinates, and one for the results.

Personal Projects - Web Developer, March 2013 - February 2015

Snow App Project - http://snow-app-project.herokuapp.com/

 Unfinished prototype web app for a project which would allow people to hire others to shovel their driveway

- Developed front-end with HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Bootstrap
- Wrote back-end with Node.js and Express.js, including registration and login functionality
- Integrated with Firebase DB

Game Project - http://kidicarus1337.github.io/Game-Project/public

- Unfinished text-based game developed in my free time for experience
- Developed front-end with HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery

J.J. Keller - Data Entry, Fall 2012 - February 2013

• Helped migrate customer information to a new server setup

Shopko - Customer Service, Fall 2008 - Fall 2012

- Primarily worked as a cashier and store front stocker
- Occasionally did some miscellaneous work

Education

Codeacademy, 2013

- HTML & CSS
- JavaScript
- jQuery
- Web Projects

Udacity, 2012 - 2013

- CS101 Intro to Computer Science
- CS253 Web Development

High School Graduate, 2006 - 2010

References

- Technical: Caleb Madrigal
 - Cell: 618-334-1919
 - Email: caleb.madrigal@gmail.com
- Character: Jeff Krumrei
 - Cell: 734-716-8977
 - Email: krumreij@gmail.com
- Character: John McNeill
 - Cell: 920-342-6259
 - Email: john.mcneill655@gmail.com